



# BIOGRAPHY

6+ years industry experience, client & agency side, working across both the public & private sectors for organisations of all shapes and sizes. A versatile strategist with brand, creative, comms and digital (web / app, social & CRM) experience. And an appetite to keep up with the latest 'goings-on' — news, tech, trends etc.

## **EXPERIENCE**

## STRATEGIST (MW > SNR)

Mr B & Friends | Mar 2019 - Mar 2021

Accounts included: Accoya (Dutch wood), Verne Global (Icelandic data centre), Regina (Ioo roll), TLT (law firm)

#### STRATEGIST (JNR > MW)

Great State | May 2016 - Feb 2019

Accounts included: Arthritis Research UK, Bristol Airport,
Orange, The Royal Navy, UNHCR (UN refugee agency)

## CREATIVE

buffalozoo | Oct 2015 - Mar 2016

Accounts included: Bristol Airport, Direct Line Group, Heathrow Airport, National Trust, Three

# **QUALIFICATIONS**

#### ADVERTISING WITH MARCOMMS

Bournemouth University | 2011 - 2015

1st. 'Best Overall Paper' for dissertation. Published in academic journal twice. Account planner of the year

#### A LEVELS & GCSES

Kingdown School | 2004 - 2011

Maths — A, Psychology — A, Biology — C 5 A\*s (equivalent), 4 As and 2 Bs

#### MISC.

The School of Life | 1993 - Present

Abstained from coffee for 365 days in 2018. MTB chariot racing world champion. Author of Furlough Diaries.

# INTERESTS



I'm also interested in exploring new places and experiencing new cultures (see map >)



## **TESTIMONIALS**

Matt Boffey | MD, London Strategy Unit "Not afraid of a blank piece of paper"

Ben Kay | Planning Director, WPP
"Equal amounts of diligence, commitment, intelligence and good humour"

## **SKILLS**

Research
Literal thinking
Lateral thinking
Problem-solving
Communication

